<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on Data Management Training</title>
    <link>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on Data Management Training</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:45:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Excel Functions</title>
      <link>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/advanced-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:45:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/advanced-excel/</guid>
      <description>In this course, the participants will learn advanced Excel functions that will help them manage and analyse data more efficiently. They will learn about VLOOKUP, IF statements, and PivotTables, enabling them to match data from one worksheet to another, analyse data based on conditions, and summarize and analyse large amounts of data.
Components 🔗 Data Validation: This video will cover how to use data validation to control the type of data that can be entered into a cell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis with Google Sheets</title>
      <link>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/google-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:45:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/google-sheets/</guid>
      <description>In this course, the participants will learn how to import data from Google Forms into Google Sheets and perform basic data analysis. They will understand how to sort and filter data, use functions like COUNTIF and AVERAGEIF, and create pivot tables. They will also be able to create charts and graphs in Google Sheets and use conditional formatting to highlight important data.
Components 🔗 Introduction to Google Sheets: In this video, the participants will be introduced to the interface and features of Google Sheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Collection with Google Forms</title>
      <link>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/google-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:45:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/google-forms/</guid>
      <description>In this course, the participants will learn how to create online surveys and quizzes using Google Forms. They will be able to create a new form, add questions and response options, and customize the form theme. They will also know how to share the form and view responses.
Components 🔗 Creating a new form: In this video, participants will learn how to create a new form in Google Forms. They will understand the different question types available and learn how to add questions and response options to the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualisation (Short Course)</title>
      <link>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/data-visualisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:45:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/data-visualisation/</guid>
      <description>In this short course, the participants will learn the basics of data visualisation along with good practices for making effective charts using Excel. They will understand how to choose the right chart type for different types of data and how to avoid common pitfalls.
Components 🔗 Introduction to Data Visualization: In this video, the participants will be introduced to the concept of data visualization, why it is important, and the principles of effective data visualization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Excel</title>
      <link>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/intro-to-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:45:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wbdatamgmt.github.io/course/intro-to-excel/</guid>
      <description>In this course, the participants will learn the basics of Excel, including how to navigate the interface, create and format spreadsheets, enter and format data, and adjust column widths and row heights. They will also become familiar with basic mathematical functions such as SUM, AVERAGE, COUNT, and MAX/MIN.
Components 🔗 Introduction to Excel: This video will provide an overview of what Excel is, what it can be used for, and what the interface looks like.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
